Front End Developer

Based in Los Angeles, CA Phone: 310-463-8890 Email: flahlee@gmail.com

# Front End Development

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

jQuery

Bootstrap

SASS

WordPress

## Version Control

Git

GitHub

#### Adobe Creative Cloud

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

#### Personal Skills

Analytical and problem solving skills

Adaptable and self-motivated

Strong business partner focus

Effective organizational skills

Quality minded

Eye for design

Ability to multitask

Team oriented

Detail oriented

Bilingual

### About me

I am a web developer with a passion of bringing new concepts, ideas and layouts to life from scratch. Main area of expertises is front-end development and everything related to web functionality. Using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, I build fast and interactive websites. My focus is to create responsive websites of high quality.

### Education

- Coding Dojo | Burbank CA | 2017-2018 | SoftwareEngineer
- UCLA Extension | WestLA CA | 2014-2016 | Design Communication Arts
- Santa Monica College | SantaMonica CA | 2010-2013 | GraphicDesign / WebDesign

## Work Experience

Company: Kobe Digital

(Oct 2018 - Current)

Title: Front End Developer

Responsible for developing and managing websites for clients on various platforms. My role is to develop only the front-end with best practice. Our clients websites vary from e-commerce to just an informational pages. My goal is always to bring a good user experience. Simplicity is the key of my code game. I am also responsible for testing the website once it is developed.

Company: Pinkette Clothing Inc.

(2014-2017)

Title: Electronic Data Interchange (EDI) Analyst

Manager of electronic data interchange systems between customers, inter-company users and vendors. Responsible for managing all orders received from our wholesale clients. Make sure everything is being shipped out on time and all orders are linked in the system. Maintained good relationship with trading partners for the company including but not limited to (Nordstrom, Bloomingdale's, Macy's, VonMaur, Forever21).

### Skills

- Front-end functionality of websites with HTML, CSS, jQuery and JavaScript
- Experience with CSS animations and transitions
- Knowledge using SCSS/SASS
- Knowledge of Bootstrap
- Common layouts using CSS Grid
- Experience with WordPress/ WooCommerce
- Good practice of image optimization, minify and compress CSS/JS files
- Good understanding of Git and command line tools
- Experience building mobile first responsive websites
- Great knowledge of Photoshop/ Illustrator/ SVG
- Work in a fast-paced environment with more than one priority
- Small to medium scale websites and web applications from scratch
- Ability to work with different projects simultaneously